<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="day_texts">
        <item>Set 5 reasons why you want to pass the bar exam. Write these reasons on a sheet of paper or a post it note and keep it near your study area every day.
 </item>
        <item>Write down: \"I am passing this test!\" 5 times on a piece of paper
 </item>
        <item>On a post it note write: \n(1) I am passing this test \n(2) I am passing this test \n(3) I am passing this test \nPut this post it note somewhere you will see on a daily basis
 </item>
        <item>First thing in the morning, go to the mirror and while you look directly into your soul (or eyes) say: \"I am passing this test\" three times.
 </item>
        <item>You are slowly building your confidence for test day. Now close your eyes for a few minutes and visualize yourself working tirelessly to master this exam.
 </item>
        <item>Now, do jumping jacks, push-ups, jump up and down, or whatever exercise you want to do to get your blood flowing. While you are moving around, chant: "I will pass this test!"
 </item>
        <item>You just finished up your first week! Close your eyes and reflect on your successes and areas of potential improvement. See yourself getting better and more confident with the material. It is still early!
 </item>
        <item>Back at it! Go back to your 5 reasons why you want to pass the bar exam. Read them over and really internalize them. You want to know your why so you can keep going through the tough days
 </item>
        <item>Back to getting the blood pumping! Do some burpies, jumping jacks, squats, or any exercise and chant postitive affirmations. \"I am intelligent, I will pass, etc.\"
 </item>
        <item>Today be mindful of the process. The bar is a marathon. Close your eyes for a few minutes and breathe deeply. Think about this two week process and how great you will feel knowing you gave this test everything you had!
 </item>
        <item>Keep it simple. Go back to the mirror and tell yourself: \"I am passing this test!\" Say it three times confidently. Do until you believe yourself and start your studying for the morning.
 </item>
        <item>You are capable of beating this test! Write down three affirmations such as: \"I am intelligent, I am hard working, I will pass.\"
 </item>
        <item>Shock your body today! I like the cold shower but that isn\'t for everyone. You can hop in a cold shower for 30 seconds, splash cold water on your face or hop in an ice bath if you are bold. When the cold hits your body, again, say: "I will pass this test!" three times
 </item>
        <item>Thirteen days down. What are you doing right and what can you improve? Are you feeling the struggle? You should feel the struggle but not feel worn down. Are you writing enough essays and multiple choice? Adjust your studying to set yourself up for success. You got this!
 </item>
        <item>Back to getting the blood pumping! Choose your exercise and while in motion, chant \"I am passing this exam!\"
 </item>
        <item>Try the cold exposure again. You can prep your breakfast and warm cup of coffee so you have something to look forward to. Hop in the cold shower or splash your face with cold water and say \"I will pass this test!\"
 </item>
        <item>Close your eyes for a few minutes and see yourself being successful on this test. You finished law school so you are more than capable! You sit down and write great essays and breeze through multiple choice. You get your results back and YOUR NAME appears on the pass list! Feel it. Now work for it, you got it!
 </item>
        <item>Go to the mirror this morning and chant: \"I am passing this test!\" three times. This process should be feeling more comfortable and your confidence is improving whether you believe it or not!
 </item>
        <item>Go for a walk today. Whether that be outside, in your study room, or at your friend\'s place. You don\'t have to say it aloud, but in your head think, \"I am passing this test, I can do it, I am more than capable!\"
 </item>
        <item>Close your eyes this morning and be thankful for your intelligence and hard work. Don\'t put too much pressure on yourself. Just breathe and be grateful for this process and that you will give it everything you got!
 </item>
        <item>No chants today. Just take out some paper or on your notebook write: "I am passing this test!" Write it down three times. Look at it, believe it, and get back to the studying.
 </item>
        <item>Exercise time! Do your Richard Simmons and get moving! Jumping jacks, push ups, jog in place, it is all fine. While you are moving chanting \"I will pass this test!\"
 </item>
        <item>The favorite day! More cold exposure. Hop in the ice bath, cold shower, or splash cold water on your face and tell yourself you are passing the test!
 </item>
        <item>Look into those beautiful eyes of yours and tell yourself: \"I am passing this test!\" Sure you may be tired of saying it, but it helps! This test is 90% mental.
 </item>
        <item>Close your eyes. You can sit or lie down. Say to yourself: \"I am confident, I will pass, I am smart enough, I have putting in the work.\" Take 5 deep breathes and open your eyes, ready to seize the day!
 </item>
        <item>Go for a walk or pace back and forth, and think to yourself: "I will pass this test."
 </item>
        <item>Close your eyes and say \"I will pass this test\" 10 times in your head and then take 5 deep breaths. You are ready for another productive day!
 </item>
        <item>Look at the 5 reasons why you want to pass the bar exam. You have almost made it through an entire month! One down, one to go. Keep striving to beat the test and you achieve success!
 </item>
        <item>Again, write: \"I am passing this test!\" three times on a sheet of paper. Take that confidence into studying and into the test center and you will be happy with your result.
 </item>
        <item>See yourself watching into the test centers. Thousands of people anxiously awaiting the test. You are prepared and confident so you chant on the way to the test center: \"I will pass, I will pass, I will pass.\" You walk to your seat and focused on your task. Don\'t worry about others. You got this! Take 3 deep breaths and get it done!
 </item>
    </string-array>







</resources>
